<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Amazon API Gateway on Express Serverless Platform</title>
    <link>https://www.express-serverless.io/tags/amazon-api-gateway/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Amazon API Gateway on Express Serverless Platform</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 29 Nov 2018 01:08:42 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://www.express-serverless.io/tags/amazon-api-gateway/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>ESP vs AWS Lambda</title>
      <link>https://www.express-serverless.io/resources/microservices-platform-comparison-express-serverless-on-aws-vs-lambda/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Nov 2018 01:08:42 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.express-serverless.io/resources/microservices-platform-comparison-express-serverless-on-aws-vs-lambda/</guid>
      <description>Developer Challenges of Serverless and AWS AWS pioneered the idea behind serverless when they introduced AWS Lambda: focus on your business logic down to its atomic parts of your applications—functions—and let them worry about the rest. This whole idea eventually led to the NoOps movement.
&amp;nbsp;
Serverless is a great idea! It&amp;#8217;s a new paradigm that can be applied to how modern applications are developed and run in the cloud to drastically increase developer focus and productivity.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>API Gateway Comparison – Features and Pricing of Amazon AWS API Gateway and Express Gateway</title>
      <link>https://www.express-serverless.io/blog/compare-amazon-aws-api-gateway-express-features/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Jan 2018 13:30:58 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.express-serverless.io/blog/compare-amazon-aws-api-gateway-express-features/</guid>
      <description>Amazon API Gateway VS. Express Gateway If you&amp;#8217;re curious about how your API Gateway stacks up, now&amp;#8217;s the time to listen up because we&amp;#8217;re breaking down the differences (and similarities) of the most popular projects for the API Gateway use case.
First up, we&amp;#8217;ve got Amazon API Gateway and we&amp;#8217;re going to compare it toExpress Gateway, an open source API Gateway built entirely on Express.js.
&amp;nbsp;
TLDR: You can skip ahead to the deep dive.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>