<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>microservices on Express Serverless Platform</title>
    <link>https://www.express-serverless.io/tags/microservices/</link>
    <description>Recent content in microservices on Express Serverless Platform</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 09 Oct 2018 00:12:30 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://www.express-serverless.io/tags/microservices/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>LunchBadger Platform is now Express Serverless Platform</title>
      <link>https://www.express-serverless.io/blog/express-serverless-platform-lunchbadger/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Oct 2018 00:12:30 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.express-serverless.io/blog/express-serverless-platform-lunchbadger/</guid>
      <description>Express Serverless Platform has arrived! After three long months of hard work, we&amp;#8217;re proud to announce that the LunchBadger Platform is now the Express Serverless Platform. New name, new features and an opportunity to experience a visual canvas ripe with all the important functionality that developers need, without the hype.
&amp;nbsp;
TLDR: Install ESP right over here
&amp;nbsp;
For Developers, DevOps teams and CTOs driving impact in top companies, it&amp;#8217;s not just a name change &amp;#8211; it&amp;#8217;s a game changer and we can&amp;#8217;t wait to show you why.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>API Gateways Comparison – Features and Pricing of Tyk API Gateway vs. Express Gateway</title>
      <link>https://www.express-serverless.io/blog/compare-tyk-api-gateway-express-features/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2018 13:42:54 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.express-serverless.io/blog/compare-tyk-api-gateway-express-features/</guid>
      <description>Tyk API Gateway VS. Express Gateway Open source: beyond the pretty packaging. There are a lot of choices when it comes to choosing and API Gateway. If you&amp;#8217;re considering a new API strategy or just kicking the tires, we&amp;#8217;ve found that it&amp;#8217;s tough find hype-free information that actually helps understand what to look for in an API Gateway and how it fits into even traditional Microservices architecture. So, we rallied the community of developers, executives and thought leaders to get the skinny on the differences (and similarities) of the most popular projects for the API Gateway use case.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>API Gateways Comparison: Features &amp; Pricing of Kong vs. Express Gateway</title>
      <link>https://www.express-serverless.io/blog/compare-kong-api-gateway-express-features/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Jan 2018 14:10:49 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.express-serverless.io/blog/compare-kong-api-gateway-express-features/</guid>
      <description>Kong API Gateway VS. Express Gateway Two popular open source projects &amp;#8211; two very different approaches. We&amp;#8217;ve gotten a lot of questions about what to look for in an API Gateway, what is an API Gateway and even how an API gateway fits into your Microservices architecture. So, let&amp;#8217;s take a deeper look at all of this and more as we break down the differences (and similarities) of the most popular projects for the API Gateway use case.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>API Gateway Comparison – Features and Pricing of Amazon AWS API Gateway and Express Gateway</title>
      <link>https://www.express-serverless.io/blog/compare-amazon-aws-api-gateway-express-features/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Jan 2018 13:30:58 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.express-serverless.io/blog/compare-amazon-aws-api-gateway-express-features/</guid>
      <description>Amazon API Gateway VS. Express Gateway If you&amp;#8217;re curious about how your API Gateway stacks up, now&amp;#8217;s the time to listen up because we&amp;#8217;re breaking down the differences (and similarities) of the most popular projects for the API Gateway use case.
First up, we&amp;#8217;ve got Amazon API Gateway and we&amp;#8217;re going to compare it toExpress Gateway, an open source API Gateway built entirely on Express.js.
&amp;nbsp;
TLDR: You can skip ahead to the deep dive.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How you can use a Multi-cloud Strategy to Grow your Company</title>
      <link>https://www.express-serverless.io/blog/can-use-multi-cloud-strategy-grow-company/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jan 2018 15:42:13 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.express-serverless.io/blog/can-use-multi-cloud-strategy-grow-company/</guid>
      <description>Over the last few months it seems like everyone has been getting in on that hot multi-cloud action. Unlike a lot of other companies, we&amp;#8217;ve been cloud agnostic since day one (before it was cool). So for LunchBadger, we&amp;#8217;d like like to take a moment and get on the mic about what this is really all about and how you can use a multi-cloud strategy to achieve maximum growth, sustainably.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>