<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Development on Express Serverless Platform</title>
    <link>https://www.express-serverless.io/categories/development/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Development on Express Serverless Platform</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 08 Nov 2018 09:09:25 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://www.express-serverless.io/categories/development/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>How To Get Started with API Management and Express Serverless Platform</title>
      <link>https://www.express-serverless.io/blog/get-started-api-management-express-serverless-platform/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Nov 2018 12:21:22 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.express-serverless.io/blog/get-started-api-management-express-serverless-platform/</guid>
      <description>In our last post, we discussed API Management and the key role that an API Gateway could play. API Gateways can enable secure access to its API endpoints. Features in an API Gateway are often categorized in three broad categories:
 Authentication: Who is allowed to access (Access Control) Authorization: Who is allowed to perform operations of exposed APIs (Permissions / Privileges) Audit: Analyzing sufficient information for each client request   How does this work?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>API Management - Setting Up Key-Based Authentication</title>
      <link>https://www.express-serverless.io/blog/api-management-setting-up-key-based-authentication-with-express-serverless-platform/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Nov 2018 09:09:25 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.express-serverless.io/blog/api-management-setting-up-key-based-authentication-with-express-serverless-platform/</guid>
      <description>We&amp;#8217;ve discussed API Management and setting up the Service and API Endpoints. As long time champions of all the ways you could be using an API Gateway, we&amp;#8217;re going to walk through how take the next step with API Management and set up your Authentication.
To recap, features in an API Gateway are often categorized in three broad categories:
 Authentication: Who is allowed to access (Access Control) Authorization: Who is allowed to perform operations of exposed APIs (Permissions / Privileges) Audit: Analyzing sufficient information for each client request   Here&amp;#8217;s a quick diagram of what that looks like:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How you can use a Multi-cloud Strategy to Grow your Company</title>
      <link>https://www.express-serverless.io/blog/can-use-multi-cloud-strategy-grow-company/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jan 2018 15:42:13 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.express-serverless.io/blog/can-use-multi-cloud-strategy-grow-company/</guid>
      <description>Over the last few months it seems like everyone has been getting in on that hot multi-cloud action. Unlike a lot of other companies, we&amp;#8217;ve been cloud agnostic since day one (before it was cool). So for LunchBadger, we&amp;#8217;d like like to take a moment and get on the mic about what this is really all about and how you can use a multi-cloud strategy to achieve maximum growth, sustainably.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>